字幕来源:william2568  校对:死亡骑士
They messed with my brain.
他们搞乱我的大脑
Thought they knew what they'd get.
他们以为已经得到了他们想要的
But they were wrong.
但他们错了
They don't know me.
他们不了解我
I don't know what happens next, but this I do know.
我不知道接下来发生了什么 但我敢肯定
You hurt me,
如果你伤害了我
I hurt you worse.
我就加倍奉还
烧脑48小时
比尔·波普 中情局驻伦敦特工
Excuse me.
借过
Hi there. My wife was in last week
你好 我的妻子上个星期
and she ordered a brown duffle in leather.
在这订了一个棕色的达尔夫皮包
We were only able to locate in black, sir.
先生 我们只进到了黑色款的
Well, she'll be very disappointed.
那么她肯定会很失望
Right.
对
Okay, thank you very much.
好的 非常感谢
- Hey, Jillie. - No, Daddy, it's Emma.
- 嘿 吉莉 - 爸爸 我是艾玛
I can't find my Elly.
我找不到我的宠物玩具
Hey, baby, we'll find it. Put Mommy on.
嘿 宝贝 会找到的 让妈妈接电话
Mommy, it's Daddy.
妈妈 爸爸的电话
- Hey, Billy. - Hey, Jillie.
- 嘿 比利 - 嘿 吉莉
When are you coming home?
你什么时候回家
That depends really. What are you wearing?
这就要看情况了 你现在穿着什么
Lingerie.
睡衣
Same thing I always wear when I pick up Emma from school.
和我平时从学校接艾玛回家时穿的一样
That explains the good grades she's been getting.
难怪老师给艾玛打的分数越来越高
Hello? Billy?
喂 比利
Urn, listen, I gotta go. I'm gonna call you back a little bit later.
呃 听着 我得走了 晚点打电话给你
All right, baby. Love you.
好吧 亲爱的 我爱你
Hey! That's my bike!
嘿 那是我的车
中情局办事处 美国驻伦敦大使馆
桂格·威尔斯 中情局驻伦敦办事处主管
So we lost him off the bridge,
我们在桥上失去了他的踪迹
but he has three options at the roundabout.
但他在环岛路上只有三个去向
Waterloo Road, Stamford Street, and Waterloo Bridge.
滑铁卢路 斯坦福大街和滑铁卢桥
He's been off the grid for 20 minutes.
他已经失联近20分钟了
I want two by twos out from the roundabout.
给我环岛路四面的监控录像
- Hey, Charlie, re-wreck every screen. - Sir.
- 嘿 查理 刷新一下显示屏 - 是
Found him.
找到他了
Bank two.
他在银行地铁站
Duffle's gone. Money's gone.
黑色皮包和钱都不见了
- Time stamp? -It's now.
- 什么时间出现的 - 就是现在
Hey.
嘿
- Where to, mate? - Just drive.
- 要去哪 - 尽管开就行
Please, thank you. Not too fast.
谢谢 不要开的太快
It's a black cab.
他上了辆黑色出租车
License number S-I-5-2-J-G-N.
牌号为SI52-JGN
I'm on him.
我去追
I-5-2...
I52…
JGN
J-G-N
沙维尔·海姆巴尔 西班牙无政府主义者
Boyd,
博伊德
William.
威廉
Can I borrow your mobile, mate? 2O quid extra.
师傅 我能借用一下你的手机吗 多给你20镑
- Borrow me phone? - Yeah.
- 你想要借我的手机 - 对
2O quid? One call, yeah?
给我20镑 只能打一个电话啊
玛塔 我是比利 不能回去找荷兰人 他们盯上我了
It's Billy.
是比利发来的
They're all over him.
他们盯上他了
Get him to the cement factory in Deptford. We used it before.
让比利引他们去德特福德 那个以前用过的水泥厂
Get a laundry team rolling, now.
现在赶快派一个清理小队过去
We're going to a cement factory. Hornlink Way, Deptford docks.
我要去一家水泥厂 在霍林科路 德特福德码头附近
I put it in your GPS, so just follow that.
我把地址输到了你的GPS里 你跟着走就行
All right.
好的
Road to destination has been calculated.
前往目的地的路线已经规划成功
The docks at Deptford.
德特福德码头
Very romantic.
真天真
Turn left at the next roundabout.
在下一个路口左转
Move, move, move.
快 快 快
Outside cement factory, sir.
报告长官 外围情况正常
- This isn't a cement factory. - Eh?
- 这不是我要去的那个水泥厂 - 你说什么
This isn't a cement factory!
这不是我要去的那个水泥厂
Hornlink Way, Deptford. I mean, the GPS don't lie, mate.
霍林科路 德特福德码头 导航仪可不会骗人
Turn around.
快掉头
Fuck!
该死的
- Do we have him? - We got nothing, sir.
- 发现了他的踪影吗 - 报告长官 什么都没发现
Nobody here.
这里没人
Do a GPS on that phone number.
定位刚刚那台手机的位置
Find him now.
给我马上找到他
If you've never been to a slaughterhouse,
要是你从来没去过屠宰场
you have to go.
你一定要去一次
To see what we do to those poor animals.
去看看那些可怜的动物遭受的折磨
They use this...
我们用这种
A picana.
电击棍
Nasty way to push them towards their doom.
用这样一种恶毒的方式结束它们的生命
Now where is our friend?
现在告诉我 我要找的那个人在哪
Billy...
比利
I respect your silence.
我敬佩你的毅力
I really do.
衷心的敬佩
The problem is,
可现在问题是
I need the Dutchman.
我要找到那个荷兰人
Last chance.
最后一次机会
Fuck you, psycho!
去死吧 疯子
Left. Go, go, go, move.
所有人行动
silent.
别出声
Point established. Just arrived on site, sir.
行动小组就绪 报告长官 我们刚刚到达现场
Check right. Check right.
检查右侧 检查右侧
North perimeter is clear.
北部外围一切正常
Bravo, copy.
B队 收到
Go. Go. Go.
上 上 上
Go.
上
- Action required. - We need a medic.
- 请求支援 - 需要急救
Confirmed: Agent Pope.
身份确认 是特工波普
Perimeter secure.
外围安全
Agent not responsive. Repeat, agent not responsive.
特工没有反应 重复一遍 特工没有反应
Respiration negative.
没有呼吸
医疗小组已经就位
Ready for defib.
准备除颤器
- Charging paddles. - Clear.
- 电极板充电 - 准备
Clear!
准备
He's dead, sir.
报告长官 他已经死了
Fuck!
该死
Doctor, I'm so sorry, but this man says he's with the government.
很抱歉 医生 但这位说他是政府派来的 一定要见你
Dr. Franks, I have one job at the moment,
法兰克斯医生 我奉命执行任务
which is to get you onto a A400 airbus sitting on a tarmac at Dover ASAP.
要立刻带你去多佛搭乘A400空客飞机
Your memory program is going live.
你的记忆项目要派上用场了
We have an officer down and we need what only he knew.
我们有一位特工牺牲了 我们要知道只有他才知道的消息
You're going to retrieve it for us.
你的任务是帮助我们找回这个信息
Does he have any brain activity?
他还有脑活动吗
That was taken a few hours ago.
这是几小时前的检查结果
I am five years away from human trials.
我已经有五年没做过人体试验了
You have 48 hours to make this work.
你有四十八小时找回这条情报
National security threat, highest level.
事关国家安全 最高级别
Can you or can you not transfer memories
你能否做到把死去哺乳动物的记忆
from a dead mammal to a live one?
转移到活体动物身上
Yeah.
可以
What do you need?
你需要什么
I'll need my equipment, I'll need my staff,
我需要我的仪器 工作人员
I'll need a suitable, uh, recipient.
和一个合适的受体
Do you have any candidates?
有候选人吗
Um, they're not gonna like him.
有 但是你们肯定不会喜欢他的
美国西弗吉尼亚州 黑泽尔顿联邦监狱
Just so wherever you're taking him knows...
希望接收他的地方心里有底
Jerico Stewart. He's in and out of prison more than half his life.
杰瑞科·斯图尔特 大半辈子都是监狱里的常客
He's got no impulse control, no sense of proportion.
他不懂如何控制自己的情绪 做事毫无分寸
He's unable to calculate
他无法估计出
the potential negative consequences of his actions.
自己的行为会带来哪些负面的影响
He has a total lack of empathy for anybody or anything.
他对任何人 任何东西都毫无怜悯之心
Through.
打开二号门
He feels nothing.
他没有感情
No hatred,
不懂憎恨
no love.
也不懂爱
It gets worse.
而且情况越来越糟
This is what was left of a gang member who tried to recruit him.
这就是试图拉他入伙的帮派成员的下场
Truth is,
说句实话
I have no way to discipline him.
我也没有办法管教他
You can't punish someone who doesn't know they did anything wrong.
惩罚一个不知道自己错在哪的人是毫无作用的
He does not understand society
他不懂社会规则
or how people are supposed to behave.
不知道哪些行为举止才是正常的
Come on.
快点给我吃的
- Hey, Jerico. - Come on.
- 嘿 杰瑞科 - 快点
These men are here to see you.
这是人是来找你的
They're taking you out.
他们要把你带走
I haven't had my lunch.
我还没吃我的午饭呢
That's right. Get Jerico his lunch.
好吧 给杰瑞科拿饭来
- Yeah. - Send in the lunch.
- 这就对了 - 把午饭给他
That's right,
这就对了
get Jerico his lunch.
给杰瑞科拿饭来
Lunch in the hole.
饭送进去了
Come on.
快
All right, enough of this shit. Lunch is over.
行了 闹够了 午餐时间结束
You're coming with us now. Let's go.
你得跟我们走了 走吧
I can't.
不行
I got a chain around my neck.
我脖子上有铁链
You know you're gonna have to use two of those.
你知道要用两发才有效
Yeah!
真好玩
You fuckers.
你们这群混蛋
Oh, you fuckers.
Got him.
好了
That's it. Open the cell.
行了 打开牢房
Go!
上
Chopper Gamma EMHG special,
G-EMHE特种直升机
you are clear for approach on runway 2-2-Lima.
你们可以在22L跑道降落
You better wake him up.
你们最好把他弄醒
美国特拉华州 多佛空军基地
Give this to the doctor.
把这个交给医生
Any allergies, Jerico?
你有过敏史吗 杰瑞科
- What? - Anything you're allergic to?
- 你说啥 - 你对什么过敏吗
Yeah, luck.
我对运气过敏
Good kind or the bad kind?
好运还是霉运
You tell me.
你说呢
We're all set, doctor.
医生 一切准备就绪
Any previous surgeries?
以前动过手术吗
Previous?
以前
I don't need no surgery...
我没病不需要手术
All right, hit him with 150 mg of hydroxyzine.
好了 给他注射150毫克安泰乐
- That's enough of this. - 150. Yes, sir.
- 让他安静点 - 150毫克 明白
What are you doing to me?
你要对我做什么
You had an injury to your head.
你头上有个伤口
You got hurt, right? When you were young.
在小的时候你受过伤 对吧
You remember how it happened?
你还记得你是怎么受伤的吗
Yeah. My mother...
记得啊 我妈
told my Daddy that he wasn't my daddy.
告诉我爸他不是我的亲生父亲
So he called her a whore
接着 他大骂我妈是个婊子
and threw me out the car window.
然后把我扔出了车外
I'm gonna take care of you, Jefico.
杰瑞科 我们会照顾好你的
: My next guest is Xavier Heimdahl.
我们的下个嘉宾是沙维尔·海姆巴尔
He's best known as the founder of Stone Harp Industries,
他最为人熟知的身份是石心集团的创立者
makers of phone, computer and communication systems.
主要研制手机 电脑和通讯系统
Most recently, he was charged with treason by the Spanish government.
最近他被西班牙政府冠上了叛国的罪名
Mr. Heimdahl, how would you respond to these very serious allegations?
海姆巴尔先生 你是如何看待这些严重的指控呢
Well, if it's treasonous to call out massive corruption at the highest levels
我认为 如果叛国罪指的是揭发最高层的大规模腐败行为
and to expose political murders...
和曝光政治谋杀案的话
Yes, then I'm guilty.
那么 我的确有罪
But your accusations were never actually proven in a court of law.
可你的指控在法庭上从未被证实过
Of course not. How could they be?
当然没有 怎么可能在大庭广众之下被证实
The police, the judges and the courts
警察 法官和法院
are all part of the world's most powerful criminal enterprise.
全都是世界上最强大的犯罪组织的一部分
Soto clarify, you're calling for the overthrow of the Spanish government.
先生 直白的说 你是要求推翻现在的西班牙政府吗
No, no, no. I'm calling for the overthrow of all governments.
不 不 不 我要求推翻世界上所有的政府组织
Politicians, religious fanatics.
政治家 宗教狂热分子
Brainwashing by corporations,
给民众洗脑的企业
the corruption of the banking system... Gone. Gone.
腐朽的银行体系 一去不复返
Washington, Berlin, Beijing will be graveyards.
像华盛顿 柏林这样的大城市 都将变成墓地
And only then people will understand
到那时人们才会意识到
there is a better way to run this world.
还有更好的运作世界的方式
And that's what you really want here, worldwide revolution.
所以你真正想要实现的是一场全球革命
Governments must fall.
必须推翻所有政府
Got one.
找到一个
Elsa Mueller. Former German Special Forces.
艾尔莎·米勒 前德国特种部队成员
One of Heimdahl's.
海姆巴尔的同伙之一
Guys, you gotta roll. Jerico Stewart is now landing.
你们该出发了 杰瑞科·斯图尔特到了
英国萨福克莱肯希斯皇家空军基地
Is Billy still breathing?
比利还有呼吸吗
Artificially breathing.
人工呼吸机
The machine's keeping his body alive but he's gone.
机器维持他身体的基本运转 但他已经死了
- You see those diodes? - Mm.
- 看到了那些二极管吗 - 嗯
They deliver a micro charge to his frontal lobe.
它们向他的额叶传送微弱的电荷
Even though his brain is clinically dead,
虽然他的大脑在临床上已经死亡
the charge fired the neurons one last time
电荷还能最后激活一次神经元
and lets us build a map of the neuronal pattern.
让我们绘制出神经元的分布图
And then you transfer it to the other guy's head?
然后你们把分布图传送到另一个人的脑袋里
No, it's not a transfer.
不对 不是传送
Jerico Stewart was chosen because he has frontal lobe syndrome,
之所以选杰瑞科做受体 是因为他患有额叶综合症
trauma to the brain when he was a child.
他小时候脑部收过创伤
Incredibly rare. One in 10 million.
非常罕见 一千万人中才出现一例
His frontal lobe remains in an undeveloped state.
他的额叶还保持着尚未开发的状态
A hotbed of neural stem cells.
能作为脑部干细胞的温床
We stimulate them with theta waves, duplicating the pattern.
我们用西塔波刺激他们 复制一样的记忆分布模式
And you've made this work?
你们以前成功过吗
Subject rats can walk straight through mazes they've never seen before.
实验鼠成功的走出了他们从没见过的迷宫
Rats.
实验老鼠
What about human trials?
人体实验呢
You're looking at it.
你正看着第一例人体试验呢
What happened to the other... other guy?
那家伙怎么了
Drilling commenced.
开始钻孔
Recipient port ready for insertion.
受体已做好插入准备
Fiber optic package ready for insertion.
光纤设备已做好插入准备
Theta waves activated.
西塔波已激活
Neural stern cell stimulation commenced.
开始刺激脑部干细胞
Testing theta.
测试西塔波
Whoa, temperature is spiking.
天啊 受体的体温正在飙升
We've got a bleed. He's at 102...
有出血 在102点上
104.
104点
Put the cold packs on him before he strokes out.
给他敷些冰袋 别让他死了
What's going on?
出什么事了
We're losing him.
他快不行了
We have to pull out the robotic arm or he's going to die.
必须赶快止血 终止手术 要不然他会死的
All right, we're going to pull the robotics, it's too much for him.
好吧 我们将机械注射器移除 他就快承受不住了
Hey! You pull nothing!
嘿 你们什么都不准撤
You carry on!
你给我继续手术
You think I give a shit if he dies?
你以为我会在乎他的死活吗
Carry on!
给我继续
He's stabilizing.
体温稳定下来了
What are we gonna tell his wife?
我们怎么向比利的妻子解释这一切
Nothing.
我们什么都不用解释
As far as she's concerned, Billy died two days ago.
对于她来说 比利十天前就去世了
It's not right.
这是不对的
Not when you come from nothing, like Billy.
而且他也远远比不上比利
Like you.
也比不上你
Jerico?
杰瑞科
Jefico!
Jefico.
杰瑞科
Jerico, take it easy, everything's fine.
杰瑞科 冷静一点 没事的
- My head. - I just gave you an injection.
- 我的头 - 我刚刚给你打了一针
It will take effect in a minute and you will feel better.
等等起效了 你就会好受一些
You swear to God?
你对天发誓
I do. You can trust me.
是的 你可以信任我
Okay, everybody out.
好了 所有人都出去
- No, no, there's a protocol... - No, not you. You stay.
- 不 不行 按照规定我必须 - 不是你 你留下
Everybody else, come on.
其他人都出去 快点
Hey, hey. Look at me.
嘿 嘿 看着我
Look at me. You know who I am?
看着我 你知道我是谁吗
My... my head's bad, I need some kind of pill.
我的头快要炸了 我要止痛药
Yeah, no, I want to give them to you.
别急 我会让他们给你的
But first, I need you to remember.
但首先你得回忆起一些事
- Remember what? - What's your name?
- 回忆什么 - 你的名字是
My...
我
- My name... - Yeah, your name.
- 我的名字 - 没错 你的名字
Your name is Bill Pope.
叫比尔·波普
Why are you messing with me, boss?
你干嘛老跟我过意不去 老大
I'm sick, doc, I need some kind of shot. I need something just...
我不舒服 给我注射点东西 我需要药
Don't, don't look at him. He can't help you.
别看他 他帮不了你
Only you can help you.
只有你才能帮你自己
Your name is Bill Pope.
听好了 你叫比尔·波普
You're an intelligence officer with the CIA.
是中情局的情报人员
Intelligence...
情报人员
What the fuck... What the fuck?
搞什么鬼 这是怎么回事
- Pay attention. - What did you do to me?
- 听我说 - 你对我做了什么
- Pay... Pay attention, all right? - What did you do to me?
- 你对我做了什么 - 听我说话
Jan Strook. Dutch programmer. Genius.
杨·斯特鲁克 荷兰籍天才程序员
- Selling trap doors to Heimdahl. - I need some water.
- 他向海姆巴尔出售了一些系统后门 - 我要喝水
That's better.
这才像话
Now...
听着
A few days ago,
几天前
The Dutchman dug a Wormhole in the deep web.
这个荷兰人在暗网里发现了一个漏洞
Will you stop this
你能停下
and give me a moment with him?
让我给他看看吗
The man has just had major brain surgery
他脑部刚刚动了一个大手术
and he's not going to tell you anything if you kill him.
他要是死了你什么都问不出来
Suddenly the Dutchman's got his finger on the whole Command and Control.
突然间这个荷兰人掌握了整个指挥控制系统
He can fire missiles anytime, anywhere, mm?
他随时能向任何地方发射导弹
But he's in way over his head.
但事情的发展超出了他的控制范围
So the Dutchman calls you, Bill Pope.
所以这个荷兰人就找上你 比尔·波普
And he needed protection,
他需要庇护
offered to make a deal with you, Bill Pope.
提出一个交易 跟你比尔·波普做交易
I need something, please.
求求你 给我点止痛药
Aspirin. I'm being good.
一片阿斯匹灵就行 我求求你
Christ, give him an aspirin.
老天啊 给他一片阿斯匹灵
Aspirin is not good for you, but this will help.
阿斯匹灵对你不好 但是这个药能让你舒服点
Billy, we had orders to put a bullet in the Dutchman's head.
比利 上头命令我们干掉这个荷兰人
- All right? But you forced the play... - Oh, God...
- 但你改变了计划 - 老天啊
because you thought you could trust him.
因为你觉得你可以信任他
You thought you could pay him off. Remember?
我们能用钱收买他 记起来了吗
Billy, we did it your way.
比利 我们按照你的计划行事
You got him to the safe house. Remember?
你把他带到了安全屋里 记起来了吗
Anything. Billy!
记起点什么都行 比利
Where did you put him? Where is the Dutchman right now?
你把他藏到哪了 那个荷兰人现在在哪
That is all we need to know.
我们现在就想知道这个
You were headed back to him
你本来要回去找他
and you picked up the money.
你拿上了钱
You were going back to close the deal! Remember!
准备去跟他完成交易 记得吗
Remember!
记得吗
I don't remember nothing, fucker.
我什么都记不起来 混蛋
You got me confused with somebody else.
你把我跟其他人搞混了
Try family.
试试家人
Your daughter's name. Huh?
记得你女儿的名字吗
Come on, you remember. What's her name?
你肯定记得 她的名字是
Emma. Your wife, Jillian. Jill, huh?
艾玛 你的妻子 吉莉 你叫她吉儿 对吧
Come on, you dumb shit, remember!
快点 你这个废物 快想想
Something! Anything!
想起点什么 什么都行
We have nothing, absolutely fucking zero.
一点有用的情报都没有
- The science is good. - Oh, the science is shit!
- 科学理论是完全正确的 - 噢 他妈的科学
Look at the fucking science! How long you been working on this?
科学有屁用 你研究这个多久了
18 years.
18年
We want a refund.
我们要求退款
- Take out the trash. - Yes, sir.
- 把那废物带走 - 是的 长官
杨·斯特鲁克 网名"荷兰人"
石心集团
Guys, we're back to square one.
伙计们 我们又重回起点了
We start from the beginning.
从头开始查
Hey, Charlie, pull up the Dutchman video.
嘿 查理 把荷兰人的那段影片调出来
Yes, sir.
是的 长官
What a fucking mess.
真是他妈的一团糟
My name is Jan Strook.
我叫杨·斯特鲁克
My cybername is Dutchman.
我的网名是"荷兰人"
I am now the sole administrator of Vigilant Shield,
我现在是"警戒之盾"的
the Emergency Command and Control system
唯一管理员
for the United States military.
我掌控着美国军方的应急指挥控制系统
I can authorize and activate
我可以授权发射
any weapon system in your arsenal
你们武器库中的任何导弹
and I can override any standing order.
还能取消任何已经生效的命令
I will sell Wormhole back to you for asylum,
我可以把这个漏洞买给你们 我的条件是政治庇护
permanent passport, guaranteed protection
永久护照 人身安全保障
- and $10 million. - Turn it off.
- 以及一千万美元 - 关掉影片
All right, guys, let's, uh, think about this.
伙计们 我们考虑一下这个
There's Heimdahl, and the safe house, here.
海姆巴尔的安全屋在这个位子
Luggage store is here.
皮包店在这
So somewhere between these two points is the Dutchman, right?
所以荷兰人就在这两点之间 对吧
Okay, where?
现在问题是 具体在哪
Hotel, youth hostel, we'd know about.
宾馆 青年旅社 那会很快被我们发现
Homeless shelter, we've already checked.
收容所 也查过了
So where the hell is he?
所以他究竟在哪
我跟你说了多少次
You're not listening to me.
你根本没认真听过
- Hello? - Uh, Bill Pope, please.
- 你好 - 我找比尔·波普
Who's this?
你是谁
Uh, old friend. Jan Strook.
我是他的一个老朋友 杨·斯特鲁克
Is he there?
他在吗
Billy's...
比利已经
My husband's dead.
我的丈夫已经去世了
Hello?
喂
Can I have a minute, fellas?
能让我跟他说几句吗
Open your mouth.
张开嘴巴
It's a vessel dilator.
这是血管扩张剂
It will increase the blood circulation
能改善血液循环
and relieve the pressure inside your head.
减少你的脑部压力
Thanks, doc.
谢了 医生
They gonna release me now?
你们要放我走了吗
You take care of yourself.
保重
Okay.
好
Oh, fuck.
哦 见鬼
You all right?
你还好吗
One of those. I want that.
上面那种给我来一个
￡4.20.
4块2
Hey, number 11, order up.
11号 东西好了
- Hey, hey, hey. Hey! - Mm.
- 嘿 嘿 嘿 - 嗯
Go on.
来打一架啊
You're funny.
你真好笑
It's not worth the kerfuffle, man.
不值得动手动脚
Who is this guy?
这家伙是谁啊
What's wrong with your face?
你的脸怎么了
United, all right!
我的地盘我做主
- I'm taking your van. - What?
- 你的车归我了 - 你说什么
What did you say?
你说什么
I said I'm taking your van.
我说你的车归我了
Hey, this nob says he's taking our van.
嘿 这家伙在胡言乱语 他说我的车归他了
What? That's bang out of order!
什么 这人脑子有洞吧
That's out of order, mate. Now fuck off.
你病的不轻阿 现在给我滚开
Go on, jog on.
快滚
What the fuck is going on here?
怎么回事
What the fuck is that?
这他妈是怎么回事
What the fuck?
活见鬼了
- My leg! You fuck! - Martin!
- 我的腿 你这个混蛋 - 马丁
You fucking cunt!
你他妈的贱人
Who is this guy, huh?
这家伙是谁啊
My head's cold.
我的头有点冷
- The essential mix. - Bloody new.
- 半夜一点 - 混音金曲
It's the hottest deep house around the world.
带你聆听全世界最酷的热辣音乐
Now, over on BBC Radio 1xtra...
一切尽在英国广播公司流行音乐电台
The number one DJ, the legend...
DJ界第一人 传奇
DJ Solomun.
DJ 所罗门
Oh, God.
老天啊
Shh!
嘘
No!
不
Where's the money, Jill?
吉儿 那些钱在哪
No, the big bag full of money.
不 那一大袋子钱
Billy's bag.
比利有个装钱的包
I don't know.
我不知道啊
Please.
求你了
Don't make me hurt you.
别逼我伤害你
Please, you can take whatever you want.
你想拿什么都可以
Yeah, no shit.
不用你废话
You changed the PIN.
你换过识别码
The PIN code, 6969.
识别码是6969
Yeah...
没错
I know stuff.
我全都知道
无声警报
Silent alarm at the Pope house.
波普家的无声警报启动了
Security code, please.
请说出安保密码
Alpha-2365.
A2365
Emma must have hit the button again, guys. Sorry, Ruiza.
肯定是艾玛不小心碰到开关了 抱歉 鲁伊斯拉
- It's okay. - Where were you?
- 没事的 - 你去哪了
- Who's there? - It's okay.
- 谁在那儿 - 没事
Mommy's here. Mommy's here.
妈妈和你在一起
There's someone in the house!
家里有外人
My name is Jan
我是杨
Jan Strook.
杨·斯特鲁克
My cybername is Dutchman.
我的网名是"荷兰人"
I am now the sole administrator for Vigilant Shield,
我现在是"警戒之盾"的唯一管理员
the Emergency Command and Control System for the United States.
我掌控着美国军方的应急指挥控制系统
I brought you in, I made you my partner.
我让你加入 我让你成为我的搭档
I treated you like my son.
我把你当我的儿子看待
And you betrayed me.
而你却背叛了我
I am seeking to turn this control over to a responsible party.
我想找个可靠的组织 把系统托付给他们
The Americans have fucked me and now want to kill me.
美国人欺骗了我 现在想除掉我
I'm going to hunt you down
我一定要抓到你
and rip out your fucking head! You understand?
把你的心脏挖出来 你他妈听到了吗
The anarchist Heimdahl is hunting me and I,
海姆巴尔 那个无政府主义者正在四处追捕我
I can't let that crazy motherfucker get it because I am not crazy.
我不能让这个系统落入那个疯子手中 因为我还没疯
Jan.
杨
Please, come back.
回来吧
Come back home. To the cause.
回到家里 完成我们的大业
I ask for asylum in the Russian Federation.
我向俄罗斯政府寻求庇护
A permanent passport.
想搞到一张永久护照
I want a better deal than Snowden got.
我要求得到比斯诺登更好的待遇
I need guaranteed protection and $10 million.
我的条件包括人身安全保障以及一千万美金
It's not about the money, it's about my freedom.
钱都不是重点 关键是要保障我的人身自由
I will demonstrate my control over Vigilant Shield today at 6:00 p.m.
今天下午六点 我会证明我已掌握"警戒之盾"系统
距离下午六点还有九小时
明白
我们等到下午六点再做打算
看看他有多大的能耐
Jillian called the police.
吉莉安报警了
They put out a description of the intruder.
他们给出了一张入侵者的模拟画像
It matches Jerico.
与杰瑞科相符
She told them he knew personal details.
她说他知道很多个人信息
- PIN number, house security code. - You're shitting me.
- 识别码 门禁密码 - 你不是在逗我吧
I talked to him. He recognized my voice. He knew my name.
我跟他说过话 他听出了我的声音 还知道我的名字
That's fucked up.
这他妈的就糟糕了
The lab work came back from forensic
验尸报告出来了
and it confirmed that the two passengers in the vehicle
他们确认 车上的两名死者
were officers Pfeffer and Butler.
是普特勒和巴特勒警官
But the third passenger in the car was not Jerico.
但车上的第三位死者不是杰瑞科
Well, we gotta find him.
那我们得赶快抓住他了
All right, what we got?
好吧 让我瞧瞧
We got trash for cash.
都是些换不到钱的垃圾
Nice.
很好
What?
怎么啦
Let's go.
动作快点
I'm hungry.
我饿了
Yeah, thanks.
谢谢
Hi. Can I have those, and I'll have a vanilla coffee...
你好 我还要一杯这种饮料 再加一杯香草咖啡
- Bonjour, Francoise. - Bonjour.
- 你好 弗朗索娃 - 你好
- 你好 - 我要一杯西柚汁 甜面包 再加一杯咖啡
稍等
What'd I just say?
我刚刚说了什么来着
Pamplemousse, grapefruit.
你说你要一杯西柚汁
Boule, sweet roll, and coffee.
甜面包 再加一杯咖啡
I'm speaking Spanish, motherfucker.
我会说西班牙语 你个小样儿
It's French... motherfucker.
那是法语 你个蠢货
Merci.
谢谢
I don't think we met.
我不觉得我们以前见过
- Anybody else? - Did you see that?
- 谁还想来跟我打一架 - 你看见了吗
Anybody else?
谁还想来
打电话叫警察
Oh. Good.
不错有吃的了
Who punches someone in a patisserie? You animal!
你个野蛮人 你怎么能随便打人
Anybody else?
还有谁吗
Want to talk about it over a motherfucking latte?
我们喝杯他妈的拿铁一起聊聊
I think he broke my nose. Oh, my God. It hurts.
你好像把我鼻子打断了 哦 天啊 真痛
Are you all right?
你还好吗
No, I'm not all right!
不 一点都不好
Hey.
嘿
Hey, you got any, uh, George Orwell books here?
嘿 你这有乔治·奥威尔的书吗
There's a queue, sir, if you wouldn't mind.
先生 如果您不介意的话 请排队
That's right. And I'm at the front of it, sugar puss.
好 我就站在第一个了 你这麻烦的婆娘
Maybe you can tell me where this Orwell guy is.
快点告诉我那个家伙的书在哪
- 4th floor. Section 41. - 4th floor.
- 在4楼 41区 - 4楼
4th floor. 4th floor.
4楼 4楼
Sorry.
非常抱歉
This ain't right.
不对啊
Where's the bag, Billy?
你的包在哪呢 比利
Where's the bag?
你的包呢
Oh, God.
天啊
Guys, someone's logged in as Billy.
伙计们 有人用比利的账号登陆了我们的系统
That must be Jerico.
一定是杰瑞科干的
- Christ, block it! - Shut it down!
- 老天爷 赶快锁住系统 - 关闭账户
No, leave him in there.
不 不用管他
I want to see what he's looking for.
我倒想看看他在找什么
I can't get in the account. He's locked us out.
我无法访问他的账号 他把我锁在外面了
What's the access point?
账号登陆地点在哪
A terminal. London public library.
伦敦公共图书馆的电脑终端
- It's this one. - It's this one.
- 就是这台 - 这台
Okay... um...
好的
Looks like he accessed our phone tracking software.
似乎他使用了我们的电话追踪软件
Dr. Franks.
法兰克斯医生
- Hello? - It's Quaker.
- 你好 - 我是桂格
Jeric0's on his way to you.
杰瑞科去找你了
We have your location. Do not hang up.
我们能追踪你 不要挂断电话
Do you understand me?
明白了吗
Do not hang up!
不要挂电话
I understand.
我明白了
What's up, doc?
医生 好久不见
I need more of those pills, all right?
上回的药再给我一些
Because without them, when I remember Bill Pope stuff,
没有那些药 我一想起比尔·波普的事
it's like my head's being crushed from the fucking inside!
脑袋就像要爆炸一样
- You remember? - Do I remember?
- 你记起来了 - 我想起来了吗
My fucking skull's splitting apart, and so is yours gonna be
我的头都快裂成两半了
unless you figure out how to help me.
你不想办法解决 你的头也会裂成两半
Yeah, of course. Yes, yes, of course.
好 没问题 好的 当然没问题
Well, where to?
现在去哪
Where to? I'm not hearing anything.
现在去哪 我在等你回答我
- A pharmacy. D-down the road. - Good.
- 去附近的药店 往那边走 - 这就对了
Let's go.
快走
Hello, Dr. Franks.
你好啊 法兰克斯医生
Hey.
嘿
Hey. Faster the fuck up.
嘿 狗娘养的 给我快点
That was mean, I'm sorry.
抱歉 我不该骂人
You hear that? I'm not sorry.
你听见了吗 我才不抱歉
That's Billy talking, not me. This guy's fucking up my game.
那是比利说的 不是我 他总是坏我的好事
Billy Pope's personality is affecting your behavior. Goddamn.
比尔·波普的人格正在影响着你的行为
I don't know about Billy, all right? I don't know about that shit.
我才不认识比利 我才不认识那死人
All I know is that I'm living this.
我只知道 我还活着
I can do stuff. It was you, all right?
我还能做事 这都是你弄的 对吗
You're the one that put stuff in my head. I tracked you down.
是你把那些东西塞到我脑子里的 我查过你了
You have skill sets?
你拥有了他的能力
That's right. I do math now. I talk languages.
没错 现在我会算数了 我会说其他语言
I go where I want, I do what I want.
我想去哪就去哪 想做什么就做什么
Everything's different. I'm brand-new.
我脱胎换骨 焕然一新
Are these memories chronological?
你的记忆是时序性的吗
I don't know. It's kicked off by shit I see, smells.
我不知道 有时我看到什么 闻到什么
You know, sometimes stuff just blurts out.
记忆就会一下子涌现出来
Please, I just need one of those pills.
求求你 给我一片那种药就行
- Okay. Okay. - All right. All I need is...
- 好 好 - 好 我只需要
All I need is one pill.
我只需要一片药
You're recalling Billy Pope's automatic responses to sensory stimulus.
杰瑞科 你刚刚提到的那些是比利的感官对触觉
Cognitive sense, touch, smell.
视觉 嗅觉刺激的反应
- What about emotions? - Yeah.
- 对情绪刺激有反应吗 - 有啊
I met his wife and kid.
我见了他的妻子和女儿
And?
然后呢
And there was...
然后
There was something.
发生了一些变化
What do you mean, "something"?
什么意思
People always told me that I didn't have feelings about this or that.
别人总说我对任何东西都没有感情
I didn't know what they were talking about until...
我刚开始一直不懂那是什么意思
I can't. How do you do this?
打不开 这玩意要怎么打开
It's child-proof.
这是为了防止儿童误食
What about now?
现在呢
Now it's messing me up.
现在你让我脑子更乱了
Or making you better.
这都是为了让你舒服点
It's called emotions.
你说的这些叫做"感情"
Well, whatever they are, I got no use for them.
管它是什么 反正对我没用
Not much meaning in life without them.
没有感情的生活将失去很多意义
Yeah, well. Thanks for the pills, doc.
是嘛 多谢你的药 医生
I need to run some tests on you
在你的记忆消失前
before the re-patterning starts to fade.
我得给你做些检查
Starts to fade?
记忆消退
How much, uh, time...
我还剩下 呃
... do I got?
多久时间
48 hours. I don't know.
大概48小时吧 我不确定
Maybe there's a way to make it last longer.
也许有办法再延长一会儿
Well, then I better boogie, right, doc?
那我现在得出发了 我还有不少事要做
Got shit to do. Money to find.
还有一大袋子钱等着我呢
- Money? - Yeah. Big bag full of money.
- 钱 - 没错 好大一袋子钱
What are you gonna do with money when you find it?
找到钱以后你准备用它们买什么
I don't know.
我没想好
I might.
买
buy a house, you know. Get a TV.
买一栋房子 你知道的 买个电视
Go on vacation like other people, right?
像其他人一样去度个假 没错
Of course.
那挺不错的
Here. Take what I owe you.
这是药钱
- On the house. - Cheers.
- 这次我请客 - 谢了
Cheers. Who the fuck says "cheers"?
谁他妈说谢了
Ruiza.
鲁伊斯拉
You still owe Billy ￡20 on Arsenal.
上次阿森纳的那场球你还欠比利20镑吧
Guess it's only fair you pay me, right?
现在还给我也一样 没错吧
All right, that's enough!
行了 别打了
You remember everything, right?
你什么都记得 对吧
Where's the Dutchman?
荷兰人在哪
I don't know. But I remember Mike's busted-up ankle.
我不知道 但我知道迈克的脚踝就要断了
I don't know what your men do, I don't know how they do it,
我不知道你的人平时怎么做事的
but you have got to stop hitting him,
但是你们不能再打他了
especially in the head.
尤其是不能打头
I get the point. But he's coming over here.
明白了 他马上就到我这了
So who am I dealing with in there?
我见到的这个是谁的人格
Is it Bill Pope?
比尔·波普的
No, he's Jerico. But he's influenced by Billy Pope's memories,
不 还是杰瑞科 可是他受到比尔·波普的影响
skill sets, routines.
像是记忆 技能和习惯影响了
- Routines? - Yeah, routines.
- 习惯 - 没错 习惯
Most of what we do in life is reduced to subconscious routine.
生活中很多行为久而久之会变成潜意识的习惯
It's these things that have made the leap from Bill Pope into Jerico.
就是它们将比尔·波普和杰瑞科联系在了一块
He mentioned money, a bag of it.
他提到了钱 一袋钱
It's driving him. Offer him that money,
钱驱使着他 把那些钱给他
he'll give you anything you want.
可能他就会告诉你你想知道的一切
Take him to the last place you had the Dutchman,
带他去你们最后一次见到荷兰人的地方
trigger Billy Pope's memories, and follow the trail.
刺激比尔·波普的记忆 跟着线索走就行
Source in Lubyanka Square just forwarded this to us.
卢比扬卡广场那边刚刚发来的情报
The Dutchman is trying to make a deal with the Russians.
荷兰人正在试图与俄罗斯人做交易
Says he's gonna give them proof today at 6:00 P.M.
他今天下午6点证明他对"警戒之盾"的掌控权
Did you hear that?
你听到了没
We're fucked.
我们完蛋了
Because you wanted a psychopath instead of a hero from Seal Team Six.
就因为你要选那个神经病 而不要一个海豹六队的英雄
距离下午六点还有三小时
The ransom money in the bag.
包里的钱是用来跟荷兰人交易的
You take us to the Dutchman, it's yours.
你带我们找到荷兰人 那些钱就归你了
Do we have a deal?
成交吗
That.
我还要
那个
Yeah. The beach.
没错 海边
I want that too.
那个我也要
I want to go there.
我要去那里
Okay...
好
Okay, you can go to the beach.
好的 我们会带你去海边
Now,
现在
do we have a deal?
现在成交吗
Yeah.
成交
- Don't shoot! Don't shoot! - Get your hands off him!
- 别开枪 别开枪 - 放开他
Stand down!
都给我退下
Only you can put out this fire.
只有你能了解这件事
The Dutchman. Where is he?
告诉我们荷兰人在哪
And the money's yours.
那些钱就归你了
The money's mine?
那些钱在哪
All of it.
那些钱全给你
I want to go there.
我还要去海边
And the picture. Yeah.
那照片也归你
Which way, Jerico?
杰瑞科 走哪边
Right.
走右边
往右开
伦敦城市机场
Sir, the facial recognition system just picked up a red notice.
长官 我们的面部识别系统发现了一位重要通缉犯
Pull over!
停车
Put the convict on ice and send him home.
把罪犯送回局里
- That's it? - The Dutchman's been flagged at London City airport.
- 就这样 - 荷兰人在伦敦城市机场被拦截了
MI-5 are covering him.
国安全局的人盯着他呢
We're heading over.
我们得马上赶过去
- Hey! - Hey!
- 嘿 - 嘿
Hey, my money.
嘿 把钱给我
Hey! What about my money?
我的钱呢
Elsa, he's yours now.
艾尔莎 就看你的了
I need him alive.
抓活的
I'm afraid it's not your man.
恐怕他不是你们要找的那位
I'm hit!
我中弹了
Give me the gun!
把枪给我
Don't shoot him!
别杀他
Sir, we ordered a dive team to search for Jerico's body.
长官 我们派潜水队去打捞杰瑞科的尸体
What a fucking mess.
真是他妈的一团糟
The Russians cannot be allowed to make the buy.
我们得阻止荷兰人跟俄罗斯人的交易
Blanket their embassy.
给我监视他们的大使馆
Anything in, anything out gets covered.
无论谁进出要检查
- Clear? - Yes, sir.
- 明白了吗 - 是的 长官
And that fucker Heimdahl's been up our asses from the start
海姆巴尔一直在骚扰我们
I want new passcodes,
给我换新的密码
new firewalls.
新的防火墙
- Switch to military channels, got it? - Yes, sir.
- 切换成军用频道 明白了吗 - 明白了
距下午六点还有一小时
Gunfire broke out earlier today on the Connaught Bridge,
今天早些时候康诺特大桥上爆发枪战
with five confirmed fatalities and numerous seriously injured.
枪战导致五人受伤 还有多人伤势严重
Authorities continue to search for missing bodies in the river Thames.
有关部门仍在泰晤士河中寻找失踪者遗体
I'm really sorry that I lost him.
我很抱歉我把人弄丢了
Maybe if I...
如果我能
If, if, if, if!
如果 如果
If you had kept closer tabs on the Dutchman,
如果你当初盯紧点荷兰人
maybe we'd already have the Wormhole!
现在我们说不定已经搞到漏洞了
I must say I'm not that happy at the moment, Elsa.
不得不说我现在真的很不高兴 艾尔莎
- Do you want me to leave? - No.
- 你这是赶我走吗 - 不
I apologize.
抱歉发那么大的火
Good.
没事
We need to find Jerico.
我们一定得找到杰瑞科
Mommy, can I watch TV?
妈妈 我能看电视吗
Sure, baby. Of course.
亲爱的 当然可以
What are you doing in my basement?
你在我家地下室干什么
What is all this?
这是什么情况
That belongs to Emma.
这是艾玛的梳子
Did you work with Billy?
你和比利共事过吗
I don't think anyone like him
我不觉得像他那样的人
ever would've worked with somebody like me.
我会跟我这样的人共事
They stuck Billy in my head.
他们把比利的记忆塞到了我脑子里
I got a scar. See?
看 我头上有个伤口
All the stuff that he knew, all the stuff that he could do,
他知道的一切 他会的那些技能
I got it all scrambled up inside me.
都在我的脑子里乱成一团
That's impossible.
这是不可能的
First car you two ever bought, used...
你们两个一起买的第一辆车
used Rover.
是一辆二手路虎
It smelled like fish and chips.
车里一股炸鱼薯条味
Bum clutch blew the first week.
没一个星期离合器就坏了
Cost you 1,100 quid to get it fixed.
花了你们1100块才修好
I told you.
我告诉你
They stuck his brain in me.
他们把比利的脑子装在了我身上
hat's enough.
够了
Mom?
妈妈
Mom, where are you? I'm hungry.
你在哪呢 我饿了
Just a second, baby.
亲爱的 我马上来
Sunday night.
星期天晚上
Chicken and waffles.
鸡肉和华夫饼
You do the chicken, I do the waffles.
你烤的鸡肉 我做的华夫饼
I know that she likes the syrup on the bottom only.
我知道艾玛喜欢只有饼底蘸糖浆的
I get pieces.
那些记忆支离破碎
Things Pop up...
不断涌现
Different places,
在不同的地方
I... I see things.
我 看到以前发生的事
Don't ask me how they did it, but they...
别问我他们是怎么做到的 但是
...they did it.
他们就是做到了
Why?
为什么
Oh, God.
噢 天啊
They're looking for details about where your husband stashed a guy
他们在找一个人 你丈夫把他藏了起来
before he was killed.
在他被杀前
Now, go feed your kid. I'll finish here and...
现在去做饭吧 我把这打扫一下
I'll finish here and get out.
我弄完了就走
Leave you alone.
不再打扰你
No.
不
Billy could never hurt you, Jill, so neither can I.
比利不会伤害你 所以我也不会
葡萄牙附近海域
美国海军弗吉尼亚级 SSN743核潜艇
Hot bird in tube 4, sir.
长官 导弹准备发射
- That's not possible. - Guidance system's a go!
- 这不可能 - 导航系统失灵
- Tracking system's a go! - Shut it down!
- 定位系统失灵 - 关闭整个系统
I can't! We're locked out, sir!
无法关闭 系统被锁定了 长官
Missile away! Repeat! Missile away!
导弹已发射 重复一遍 导弹已发射
Punch in the self-destruct code before the fish can arm itself!
在爆炸前快输入自毁代码
A30 E40 BH
Alpha 30, echo 40, Bravo Hotel.
Negative. It's not responding.
自毁代码无效 没有反应
导弹终止
We're good. No nuke flash. We're good.
导弹已自毁 未见核爆光
Jesus fucking Christ.
老天爷啊
We didn't terminate that missile, sir.
导弹不是我们终止的 长官
Did you know I lost my Daddy?
你知道我的父亲去世了吗
Yeah.
我知道
He gave me Elly. For my birthday.
艾丽是他送我的生日礼物
If we don't go deeper, his trunk's gonna stick out.
不挖深一点 她的象鼻子就会露出来
Go deeper.
那就挖深点吧
Did you hurt yourself?
这是你自己弄的吗
Stop.
住手
Emma, come here, please.
艾玛 到妈妈身边来好吗
No, Mommy. We're burying my Elly.
没事的妈咪 我们在埋艾丽
Come here.
快过来
He said he was a friend of Daddy's.
他说他是爸爸的一个朋友
Leave. Please.
请你离开这里
Can he stay for dinner? He's nice.
能让他留下来吃晚饭了 他人挺好的
Emma, go inside.
艾玛 到屋里去
I'll do the waffles, then I'll go.
我把华夫饼做完就走
Come and play.
过来弹琴吧
What?
你说什么
Come and play.
过来弹琴吧
I don't know how.
我不知道怎么弹琴
I'll teach you.
我来教你
I don't know if this is such a good idea.
我觉得这样好像不太好
It's fine. Come on.
没事的 来吧
- Mm-hmm. - Come on.
- 嗯 - 来吧
So you just put your hands like this.
像这样把手放在上面
Put your hand there.
把手放在这儿
And then you go...
然后开始弹
It's okay.
弹的挺好的
That's right. And then you go again.
就是这样 然后接着弹
Okay, Emma. It's late.
好了 艾玛 很晚了
It's time to go to bed.
该上床睡觉了
Yes, Mommy. Good night, Jerico.
好的 妈妈 晚安杰瑞科
- Good night, Mommy. - Good night, baby.
- 晚安 妈咪 - 晚安 亲爱的
Who are you?
你究竟是谁
I don't know.
我自己也不清楚
Most of my life, a number.
我大半辈子都只有一个编号
My brain don't always work right.
我的有时候神经不正常
I haven't always acted right.
有时做出一些异常的举动
Having your man in my head made me...
有了你丈夫的记忆后
made me feel things. Know things.
我感觉到了很多东西 学到了很多东西
Right. Wrong.
知道了是非对错
I guess it don't matter.
不过这都无关紧要了
Doc says it's all going away pretty soon.
医生说记忆很快就会消退
Can you feel what Billy felt?
你能感受到比利的感情吗
Can you?
你能吗
There was this funny thing Billy used to do.
以前比利经常做一个滑稽的手势
This is too much.
我受不了了
That was our signal that he loves me.
那个手势代表他爱着我
I, uh...
我
I know...
我知道的
I know what that
我知道
"love" word's supposed to mean, but I...
"爱"这个词字面上的意思 但我…
I never...
我从来没有
Our wedding day.
我们结婚的那天
Do you remember?
你还记得吗
Yes.
记得
The beach.
在海边
- First time I handed you Emma? - Yeah...
- 我第一次把艾玛交到你手上 - 嗯
You were so happy.
你当时是那么的开心
Yeah. I have...
是的 我…
I feel it.
我记得
我感觉到了
Yes I...
是的 我
He loves you...
他深爱着你
so much.
深爱着你
Where will you go now?
你现在要去哪
I don't know, wherever he...
我也不知道 去他
wherever he takes me.
去他的记忆带我去的地方
Then stay here.
那就留下来吧
You can stay on the couch.
你可以睡在沙发上
It won't be the first time on that couch.
应该不是第一次睡在那张沙发上了
Our top story, a mystery missile
今日要闻 一枚神秘的导弹
that was launched off the coast of Portugal.
在葡萄牙近海被发射
The question is, where'd this missile come from?
问题是 这枚导弹是从哪发射的
Our adversaries are getting more sophisticated.
我们的敌人更加复杂
Good morning.
早安
Got you some fresh coffee.
我给你煮了一些咖啡
Thanks.
谢谢
Don't worry about it.
不用太在意
It's okay.
没事的
where this missile came from,
在五角大楼给出导弹的来源前
we won't know who will be held accountable.
我们无法确定这次事件的主要负责人
This is now the smoking gun. We have radar analysis...
目前掌握的证据是雷达分析结果
伦敦大学
吉莉安·波普博士
You work at the university.
你在伦敦大学工作
There's a cage in the library, right?
图书馆里有个铁栅栏对吗
A bookcase with a key.
一个带钥匙的书柜
Yeah, the rare book collection.
是的 那里收藏稀有书籍
Billy and I used to go there sometimes.
比利和我有时会去那里
- Why? Does this have something...? - Yes.
- 怎么了 是有什么联系吗 - 是的
Yes.
没错
Everything.
有至关重要的联系
I'll need a car.
我需要一辆车
And the key for the books.
给我那个书柜的钥匙
Sure. Yeah.
好的 没问题
We're gonna have money, Jill.
吉儿 我们马上就有钱了
Lots of it.
有很多钱
I wish I could keep being him.
我真希望我能一直当他
Emma? Come upstairs, please!
艾玛 到楼上来好吗
Coming!
我来了
Come. We need to take a shower.
快来 你得洗个澡
- Did you lock the door downstairs? - Yeah.
- 你锁了楼下的门吗 - 锁了
Where is Jerico?
杰瑞科在哪
大学图书馆
You're the guy who killed me.
你就是杀了比利的那个人
Good memory.
记性不错
Yeah.
那是
You hurt me.
如果你伤害了我
I hurt you worse.
我会加倍奉还
I respect your creed.
我敬佩你的信念
Mm, good.
很好
Over there.
开到那儿
Sir, I have something.
长官 有新情况
Akhmadov. Russian FSB operative.
阿克玛多夫 俄国家安全局特工
What's he doing arriving on a fishing boat in Dagenham?
他怎么跑到达格南的一艘渔船上去了
The Russians aren't stupid enough
他们还没蠢到
to try making a move from their own embassy.
直接在自家的大使馆里采取行动
They're bringing in a grab team to pick up the Dutchman.
我明白了他们准备派一个抓捕小组去接荷兰人
Get me in the air now!
给我立即联络一架飞机
He'll be on the A11,
盯紧A11高速路
headed right toward us.
他们会朝我们过来
We follow the Russians. They'll lead us to the Dutchman.
我们跟着俄罗斯人就能找到荷兰人
I don't particularly like children.
我不是特别喜欢小孩
- They never live up to their hype. - Jefico!
- 他们总是达不到你的要求 - 杰瑞科
Jerico, help! Please!
杰瑞科 救命 求求你
Get in there.
上车
Stop! Stop! Please!
求求你们 住手
Stop.
住手
No more violence. No more violence.
不要使用暴力 不要使用暴力
Get him up.
拉他起来
Take me to the Dutchman.
带我去找荷兰人
He's in there.
他在那边
Give me thermals.
启动热能探测
The Russian grab team is in the truck.
俄罗斯抓捕小队在卡车里
We follow. Do not engage.
我们跟踪他们 不要交火
All units, we are in ghost surveillance.
所有单位注意 进行隐蔽侦查
- Do not approach. - Copy that.
- 不要靠近他们 - 收到
There. At the university.
卡车进伦敦大学校区了
Do not approach until we see the Dutchman.
在看到荷兰人之前不要靠近
All units, do not approach.
所有单位注意 不要靠近
- Copy that. Stand down. - Roger that.
- 收到 所有人待命 - 收到
Let's go.
行动
Sniper team. What's your position?
狙击分队 报告你们的位置
Sniper team on the move.
狙击小队移动中
Sir, we have a visual on Heimdahl and Jerico.
长官 我们发现了海姆巴尔和杰瑞科
- Move in! Move in! - All units, move in.
- 开始行动 - 所有单位 开始行动
Take out the Russian team. We need Jerico alive.
干掉俄国人 留杰瑞科活口
Your wife and kid just died.
你的老婆孩子死定了
Get this thing on the ground.
快让这玩意降落
No, your guy's not over there. They don't have him.
不 你要的人 不在他们手上
- What do you mean? - I just said it.
- 什么意思 - 我说了
They don't have him. All right? I just told you.
你要的人不在他们手上 我再说一遍
You tell the psycho. He's up there, all right?
你个疯子 他在那楼上 懂了吗
He's not over there. They don't have him.
你要的人 不在他们手上
I'll go. Get to the airfield. You need to get out of here.
交给我 你先去机场 你必须离开这里
Get the Dutchman. See you there.
抓到荷兰人 我在机场等你
化学实验室
Where are we going?
我们要去哪儿
Through here.
穿过那里
Jillian's office.
吉莉安的办公室
Where is he?
荷兰人在哪
In the corner office. See him?
在那个角落办公室里
甘油 硫酸
硝酸
Get out.
快跑
- Don't kill me. - Shut up.
- 别杀我 - 闭嘴
You don't know me, all right? But I know you.
你不认识我 但是我认识你
You and Pope made a deal.
你和波普做了笔交易
He's dead, but he's making it good.
他已经死了 但他死前已经把事办妥了
That's your money.
这是你的钱
That's your passport.
还有你的护照
- The passport. - The Wormhole. Where is it?
- 护照给我 - 漏洞在哪
It's in my computer.
在我的电脑里
- Set it up. - No problem.
- 打开 - 没问题
You do exactly what I tell you to do,
你按我说的去做
maybe you'll live to spend all this money.
也许还能留一条小命花这笔钱
You're a fucking genius.
你真他妈的是个天才
This is some good crazy shit right here.
这办法一般人绝对想不到
Live by the sword, die by the sword.
以其人之道还其人之身
Brilliant.
太有才了
Fuck!
见鬼
- Give me the flash drive. - I'll give you anything you want.
- 把闪存盘给我 - 你想要什么我都给你
- Come on. Don't make me wait. - Yeah. Here.
- 动作快点 少浪费时间 - 好 给你
Flash drive.
闪存盘
Thank you.
多谢了
Fuck!
该死
Fuck you...
你妈的
- Fuck you, bitch! - Painful?
- 该死的婊子 - 很痛吗
Giving Heimdahl Vigilant Shield is fucking crazy!
把"警戒之盾"交给海姆巴尔 疯子才会这么做
Elsa?
艾尔莎
I got it.
都办妥了
I'm on my way. The Dutchman and Jerico are dead.
我马上来 荷兰人和杰瑞科都死了
Good girl. I'm waiting for you.
亲爱的干得好 我在这边等你
Elsa?
艾尔莎
Fuck you.
你妈的
You need an ambulance, sir. Just wait over here.
先生你需要接受治疗 在那边等一会
I'll send the paramedic over to you immediately.
我马上叫个医生来
- Can I get paramedics? - Okay.
- 医生快来 - 好的
Who is that?
那家伙是谁
She's dead.
她已经死了
Yeah. .
找到了
Here.
接着
Take the computer. Have it scanned.
把电脑带走 查一下内容
Stolen ambulance right outside. Wounded man took it.
外面报告说一个受伤的男子 偷走了一辆救护车
Fits the description of Jerico.
嫌疑人特征与杰瑞科相符
- Jerico's got it. - On our way.
- 东西在他手上 - 快追
Somebody get me a track on that ambulance.
给我追踪那辆救护车
Elsa?
艾尔莎
Does this sound like Elsa to you, motherfucker?
我的声音听起来像艾尔莎吗 你个混蛋
- Where is she? - I beat your girlfriend up.
- 她在哪 - 我把你女朋友杀了
She's dead. Fuck her, all right?
她死了 别管她了
I got what you want.
我手上有你想要的东西
So here's what's gonna happen.
你给我仔细听好了
Are you dictating terms to me?
你这是在对我发号施令吗
That's right, psycho.
没错 疯子
Get the little girl.
把那个小女孩带过来
I'm sending you directions.
听好了
- You come here... - No,no,no.
- 你给我过来 - 不 不 不
and deliver me that flash drive.
把闪存盘交给我
Or they die. Say something.
要么我就杀了她们 说几句话
Jerico, help, he's taking me.
杰瑞科 救命 他抓住我了
- He's gonna do something. - Hey.
- 他要做坏事 - 嘿
His little one first...
小孩先上路
so her Mommy can watch.
在妈妈的目送下
Do you understand?
听懂了吗
I'm gonna fuck you up.
我非把你宰了不可
I'm gonna fuck you up!
Jerico! Jerico!
杰瑞科 杰瑞科
Do not give him the flash drive.
别把闪存盘给他
Do you understand me? He will scorch the earth.
听懂了吗 世界会毁在他手里的
You copy?
听见了吗
I got this figured out.
我已经搞清楚了
Jerico, you have nothing figured.
杰瑞科 你什么都没弄清楚
You only have half a fucking brain.
你只有一个半吊子脑袋
You are not Bill Pope.
你不是比尔·波普
He has a gun to her head, asshole, all right?
混蛋 他用枪指着她们
He has a gun to the... .
他会杀了
to the baby.
孩子的
What's her name? I can't remember her name.
那个孩子叫什么 我想不起她的名字
Emma!
艾玛
- Her name is Emma! - Patch in the ambulance radio.
- 她叫艾玛 - 接通车上的无线电
We're on. He can hear you.
接通了 他听得见
Jerico, it's Dr. Franks.
杰瑞科 我是法兰克斯医生
I think I can freeze what's left of the implant, Jerico.
我想我已经找到了保留你记忆的方式了
You can be normal.
你可以过上正常的日子
But we have to do this now, before it's gone.
赶在记忆消失前我们得立即手术
You turn around, come back here and see me.
马上掉头回来见我
What about Jillian?
那吉儿怎么办
There's too many lives at stake, Jerico.
这事关无数人的性命 杰瑞科
We're all gonna die.
我们都得死
Leave them. They don't matter.
别管她们了 她们不重要
They do to me.
她们对我很重要
Little closer.
在靠近点
Yeah!
耶
Officers down! Officers down!
有警官受伤 有警官受伤
Medical units en route. We have casualties.
医疗小组出动 这里有人受伤
He's getting close, so let's get ready.
他马上到 做好准备
Jefico!
杰瑞科
No!
不
He's got Emma.
艾玛在他手上
Put it down.
把枪放下
Put it down!
扔在地上
Give me the flash drive.
把闪存盘给我
Emma, run!
艾玛 快跑
What are the coordinates down there?
刚才那里的坐标是多少
I have a...
我要送个
little souvenir for them.
小小的纪念品给他们
确认访问密码 发射程序启动
- Quaker! - Copy!
- 桂格 - 收到
Heimdahl just fired one of our cruise missiles 60 miles north of you.
海姆巴尔刚刚在你以北六十公里处发射了一枚巡航导弹
Evacuate the area. Get out of there!
疏散那个区域 赶快撤出去
Hey! Do you have any idea what you've done? Yeah?
嘿 你知道你刚刚做了什么蠢事吗
You killed us all, you fucking asshole!
你他妈的混蛋 你把我们都害死了
Hey! What are you doing? He just got shot, for God's sake!
嘿 你在干什么 他刚中弹了 天啊
Get back! Get her out of here!
退后 快把她带走
Get her out of here!
快把她带走
Ah, you worry too much.
别操心了
I made...
我已经
I made that guy fix it.
我已经让那个家伙搞定了
- Who? - I can't remember his name.
- 谁 - 我不记得他的名字了
- Jan Strook? - No.
- 杨·斯特鲁克 - 不是
The Dutchman? The Dutchman?
荷兰人 是荷兰人吗
Yeah. Yeah.
没错 没错
Yeah, the Dutchman. He fixed it.
没错 那个荷兰人已经搞定了
- Fixed what? - He...
- 搞定了什么 - 他
Jerico! Jerico, what did the Dutchman fix?
杰瑞科你说话啊 荷兰人搞定了什么
Heimdahl's first shot.
海姆巴尔发射的第一枚导弹
Whatever it was,
不论他用什么武器
wherever he tried to send it...
不论他想攻击哪里
...it comes back for him.
都会转而攻击他
I told that motherfucker...
我跟那个混蛋说了
You hurt me,
如果你伤害了我
I hurt you worse.
我会加倍奉还
Fuck me.
见鬼
My head's cold.
我的头好冷
I'm cold.
我好冷
Are you sure about this?
你确定那能行吗
He hasn't been responding.
他一直没有反应
Maybe this will trigger something.
也许这能刺激他的记忆
If he remembers anything, he remembers it all
他只要想起一件事情 就能想起全部
and Bill Pope is here to stay.
比尔·波普的记忆就能保存下来
You might not remember me,
你可能不记得我了
but I know you.
但我认识你
It's unbelievable. He remembers.
真是难以置信 他记起来了
You gonna release him now, turn him loose?
你准备放了他吗
I'm gonna offer him a job.
我打算给他一份工作